<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joy Liu</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Joy Liu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 21:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/aboutresume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aboutresume/</guid>
      <description>About Me!My name is Joy! I was born in Dallas, Texas and I moved to Austin in 2016 for college. I graduated from the University of Texas at Austin with a Bachelor of Science and Arts in Biology and a certificate in Pre-Health Professions. I’m planning on attending the PA program at the University of Texas Medical Branch, starting in July 2020. I am really passionate about healthcare and also spreading education and awareness about current topics in medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/blog/aboutresume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/aboutresume/</guid>
      <description>About Me!My name is Joy! I was born in Dallas, Texas and I moved to Austin in 2016 for college. I graduated from the University of Texas at Austin with a Bachelor of Science and Arts in Biology and a certificate in Pre-Health Professions. I’m planning on attending the PA program at the University of Texas Medical Branch, starting in July 2020. I am really passionate about healthcare and also spreading education and awareness about current topics in medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;ve Been Learning in Python</title>
      <link>/blog/pythonstuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/pythonstuff/</guid>
      <description>Though the majority of SDS 348 was focused on getting more comfortable with R, I learned some Python at the end. Though I had already learned some Python in previous coding classes, I had never learned about regex (regular expressions) before. This method of finding parts in strings was really interesting to me!
Here’s an example of what we did in our homeworks:
Using re.findall(), match all numbers and pull them from the following string (string1).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Love About Python</title>
      <link>/2019/12/14/what-i-love-about-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/12/14/what-i-love-about-python/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Here are some projects I have been working on in my SDS348 class! Enjoy :)
  Project 1
  Project 2
  I may add more in the future!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume / About Me</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownThis is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SDS 348 Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionFor my Exploratory Data Analysis, I decided to analyze how crime statistics in states may be affected by certain variables. The first dataset I chose was the state.x77 dataset from the carData package. This dataset contains all 50 states and gives various statistics for each one, including population estimates, per capita income, life expectancy, percent of high school graduates, and land area. The second dataset I chose was the USArrests dataset from the datasets package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SDS 348 Project 2: Modeling</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionFor my second project, I decided to take a look at the dataset Arrests, found in the carData package. This dataset contains data about individuals who were arrested in Toronto for possession of marijuana. For each individual arrested, there are variables detailing the individual’s race, age, sex, employment status, whether or not they are a citizen, the year they were arrested, the number of police databases on which the arrestee’s name appeared, and whether they were released or not.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>